Okay, I see where it got its name.
好吧   我想我知道这名字的由来了
So what happened that made us avoid it all this time?
那么   这里发生了什么   我们到现在什么都没看见
Some wolves claim that it's haunted with a wolf ghost.
有些狼说这里时常出现狼的鬼魂
Is that supposed to be aggression?
这算不算是攻击
You see? Even the critters are afraid of us.
你看   这些小动物都害怕我们
Runt, unnecessary.
朗特   不必这样
Dad! If the Omegas are the kings of the forest,
爸爸   如果欧米伽是森林之王
we have to show it who's boss!
我们必须让他看看谁是老大
-Ah! -I think he just did.
-啊   -我想他想试试看
Hey, wolves, the exit's that way.
嘿狼们   出口在那边
Yeah, and the forest is that way.
是的   而森林在那边
You want to take this outside?
你想出去比划比划么
Aren't we already outside?
我们不是已经出来了吗
Dad! Come on!
爸爸 走吧
You wolves are making a big mistake.
你们狼类犯大错误了